University of Connecticut, Vice President for Academic Affairs Office Records [Anthony DiBenedetto and Julius A. Elias, 1981-1988] 1998.0154
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series XI: Schools and Colleges, undated, 1980-1990
  - Education, School of
    - Sixth Year Program: professional education, 1980 (Box 24:, Folder 696)
    - Special Education Center, 1985-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 697-699)
    - Special Olympics Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 700-701)
    - Speech and Hearing Clinic, 1986 (Box 24:, Folder 702)
    - Sport and Leisure Studies, 1983-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 703-708)
  - Engineering, School of
    - Accreditation, 1984-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 709-711)
    - Bachelor of Technology Program, 1984-1985 (Box 24:, Folder 712)
    - Budget and funding, 1987-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 713)
    - Capital equipment purchases, 1986-1987 (Box 24:, Folder 714-715)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 1983-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 716-719)
    - Civil Engineering Department, 1983-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 720-723)
    - Computer Science and Engineering Department, 1986-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 724-726)
    - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 24:, Folder 727-728)
    - Dean, 1985-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 729-731)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Department, 1983-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 732-734)
    - Electrical and Systems Engineering, 1986 (Box 24:, Folder 735)
    - Engineering Advisory Board meeting, 1987-1989 (Box 24:, Folder 736)
    - Engineering equipment, 1989 (Box 24:, Folder 737)
    - Environmental Research Institute: mobile (Box 24:, Folder 738)
      - Toxics van, 1988-1989
    - General, 1984-1987 (Box 24:, Folder 739-742)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 743-744)
    - Hazardous materials waste, 1986-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 745-746)
    - Hydraulics Laboratory, 1985 (Box 25:, Folder 747)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1983-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 748-751)
    - Metallurgy Department, 1982-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 752-755)
    - Minority Engineering Program, 1987-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 756)
    - Minority recruitment, 1988-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 757)
    - Student petition: engineering and mathematics, 1985 (Box 25:, Folder 758)
    - Undergraduate Instructional Laboratory Plan, 1987 (Box 25:, Folder 759)
    - United Technology Building, 1986-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 760)
  - Extended and Continuing Education
    - Bachelor of General Studies Program, 1983-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 761-764)
    - Budget and funding, 1983-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 765)
    - Credit programs, 1987-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 766-767)
    - Dean, 1985-1986 (Box 25:, Folder 768)
    - Fitness for Life Program, 1989 June (Box 25:, Folder 769)
    - Gale/Roper Scholarship Agreement, 1989 July (Box 25:, Folder 770)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 771-776)
    - George Washington University Agreement, 1989 August (Box 25:, Folder 777)
    - Institute of Public Service, 1986 (Box 25:, Folder 778)
    - New England Senior Academy, 1989 August (Box 25:, Folder 779)
    - Non-credit programs, 1983-1986 (Box 25:, Folder 780-781)
    - Public Affairs, Institute of, 1987-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 782)
    - Reorganization, 1987 (Box 25:, Folder 783)
    - 6012 Fund, 1984 (Box 25:, Folder 784)
  - Family Studies, School of
    - Alumni Advisory Board, 1986 (Box 25:, Folder 785)
    - Child Care Center Plans, 1986 (Box 25:, Folder 786)
    - Child Care facilities, 1986-1988 (Box 25:, Folder 787-789)
    - Dean, 1986-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 790-791)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 25:, Folder 792)
    - Flag Stabilization Project, 1985-1989 (Box 25:, Folder 793-794)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 795-801)
    - Gerontology, University Program of, 1985-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 802-803)
    - Infant - Toddler Programs, 1985-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 804-805)
    - Operating budget, 1990 (Box 26:, Folder 806)
    - Phase-out of Interior Design, 1984 (Box 26:, Folder 807)
    - Search expenses, 1985 (Box 26:, Folder 808)
  - Fine Art, School of
    - Art Department, 1983-1988 (Box 26:, Folder 809-814)
    - Budget and funding, 1988 (Box 26:, Folder 815)
    - Ceramics program, 1986-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 816)
    - Curricula and Courses Committee, undated (Box 26:, Folder 817)
    - Dean, 1985-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 818-820)
    - Dramatic Arts Department, 1982-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 821-826)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 827-832)
    - Masters of Fine Art, 1986 May (Box 26:, Folder 833)
    - Music Department, 1983-1989 (Box 26:, Folder 834-841)
    - Photographical equipment: Greenburg gift, 1989 August (Box 26:, Folder 842)
    - Shakespeare Theatre, 1986-1987 (Box 26:, Folder 843)
    - Stratford Institute, undated (Box 26:, Folder 844)
  - Graduate School
    - Budget and funding, 1988-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 845)
    - Director's office, 1986-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 846)
    - Engineering Research Center Property, 1984 (Box 27:, Folder 847)
    - Environment Health and Safety, 1985-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 848-849)
    - Executive Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 27:, Folder 850-851)
    - Fulbright Awards, 1987-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 852)
    - General, 1985-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 853-857)
    - Graduate assistants, 1983-1984 (Box 27:, Folder 858)
    - Graduate Student Senate, 1989 (Box 27:, Folder 859)
    - International Affairs reorganization, 1987 (Box 27:, Folder 860)
    - International Education, 1985-1989 (Box 27:, Folder 861-865)
    - International Student office, 1983-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 866-869)
    - International Zagazig University, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 870)
    - Master of Public Affairs Program, 1983-1985 (Box 27:, Folder 871-872)
    - McNair Post-Baccalaureate Achievement Program, 1989 (Box 27:, Folder 873)
    - Minority Fellowship, 1989 (Box 27:, Folder 874)
    - Minority Graduate Education, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 875-876)
    - Neuroscience Program, 1983-1985 (Box 27:, Folder 877-878)
    - Northeast Undersea Research Program, 1983-1984 (Box 27:, Folder 879)
    - Sea Grant Office, 1983-1988 (Box 27:, Folder 880-881)
    - Sea Grant, 1983-1985 (Box 27:, Folder 882-883)
    - Vice President for Graduate Education and Research, 1983-1985 (Box 27:, Folder 884-887)
    - Warsaw Technical University Property Agreement, 1988 (Box 27:, Folder 888)
  - Law, School of
    - Accreditation, 1984-1986 (Box 28:, Folder 889-890)
    - Admissions, 1983 (Box 28:, Folder 891)
    - Budget/funding, 1983-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 892-894)
    - Computer Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 28:, Folder 895-896)
    - Dean, 1988-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 897)
    - Gallivan Chair, 1984-1988 (Box 28:, Folder 898)
    - General, 1984-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 899-903)
    - Law Library, 1985-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 904-905)
    - Non-Discrimination Policy, 1983-1984 (Box 28:, Folder 906)
    - Renovations, 1984-1986 (Box 28:, Folder 907-909)
    - Space needs: Phase III, 1984-1986 (Box 28:, Folder 910)
    - Student-related issues, 1982-1986 (Box 28:, Folder 911)
  - Liberal Arts and Science, College of
    - African Studies Group, 1989 May (Box 28:, Folder 912)
    - AFROTC, 1989 (Box 28:, Folder 913)
    - Anthropology Department, 1983-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 914-918)
    - Armenian Studies, 1986-1988 (Box 28:, Folder 919)
    - Biobehavioral Sciences Department, 1983-1989 (Box 28:, Folder 920-925)
    - Biobehavioral Sciences Department, 1985 (Box 29:, Folder 926-927)
    - Biological Sciences Group, 1983-1986 (Box 29:, Folder 928-938)
    - Budget and funding, 1988-1989 (Box 29:, Folder 939)
    - Chemistry Department, 1983-1989 (Box 29:, Folder 940-944)
    - Communication Sciences Department, 1983-1989 (Box 29:, Folder 945-948)
    - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1988 (Box 29:, Folder 949)
    - Dean, 1983-1989 (Box 29:, Folder 950-953)
    - District Internship Program, 1982 (Box 29:, Folder 954)
    - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1984-1989 (Box 29:, Folder 955-956)
    - Economics Department, 1983-1988 (Box 29:, Folder 957-961)
    - English Department, 1983-1988 (Box 29:, Folder 962-967)
    - English Department, 1983-1988 (Box 30:, Folder 968-975)
    - Faculty Scholarship Committee, 1987 (Box 30:, Folder 976)
    - Foreign Languages Department, 1983-1984 (Box 30:, Folder 977)
    - General, 1983-1989 (Box 30:, Folder 978-982)
    - Geography Department, 1984-1989 (Box 30:, Folder 983-986)
    - Geology and Geophysics Department, 1985-1988 (Box 30:, Folder 987-988)
    - Haskins Laboratories, 1986-1989 (Box 30:, Folder 989)
    - High School Cooperative Program, 1983-1987 (Box 30:, Folder 990-992)
    - High School Science Fair, 1985-1989 (Box 30:, Folder 993)
    - History, Department of, 1983-1989 (Box 30:, Folder 994-1005)
    - Jagiellonian, 1987-1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1006)
    - Journalism Department, 1983-1988 (Box 30:, Folder 1007-1008)
    - Life Sciences, reorganization of, 1983-1984 (Box 31:, Folder 1009)
    - Linguistics Department, 1980-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 1010-1012)
    - Marine Sciences Department, 1984-1987 (Box 31:, Folder 1013)
    - Mathematics Department, 1983-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1014-1017)
    - Medieval Studies Program, 1980-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 1018)
    - Middle East Studies, 1987 (Box 31:, Folder 1019)
    - Modern and Classical Languages, 1985-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 1020-1024)
    - Molecular and Cell Biology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1025-1028)
    - New England College of Optometry/ Providence College Proposal, 1984-1985 (Box 31:, Folder 1029)
    - Philosophy Department, 1983-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 1030-1033)
    - Physiology and Neurobiology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1034-1036)
    - Physics Department, 1983-1988 (Box 31:, Folder 1037-1040)
    - Physiology and Neurobiology Department, 1985-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1041-1043)
    - Political Science Department, 1983-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1044-1047)
    - Psychology Department, 1983-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1048-1051)
    - ROTC, 1983-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1052-1055)
    - Sociology Department, 1983-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1056-1059)
    - Statistics Department, 1985-1989 (Box 31:, Folder 1060)
    - Teaching assistant stipends, 1985 (Box 31:, Folder 1061)
  - Medicine, School of
    - General, 1985 (Box 31:, Folder 1062)
  - Nursing, School of
    - Accreditation, undated (Box 32:, Folder 1063)
    - Curricula and Courses Committee, 1984-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1064)
    - Dean, 1987-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1065)
    - General, 1985-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1066-1070)
    - Implementation of the PTR Process, 1984 (Box 32:, Folder 1071)
    - Physical Therapy, undated (Box 32:, Folder 1072)
  - Pharmacy, School of
    - Accreditation, 1989 June (Box 32:, Folder 1073)
    - Clerical ratios, 1984-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1074)
    - Dean, 1987 (Box 32:, Folder 1075)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, undated (Box 32:, Folder 1076)
    - General, 1982-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1077-1082)
    - Health Center: Pharmacy Program, Farmington, 1981 (Box 32:, Folder 1083)
    - Pharm. D. Degree, 1985-1987 (Box 32:, Folder 1084-1085)
    - Toxicology Program, 1985-1987 (Box 32:, Folder 1086-1087)
  - Social Work, School of
    - Accreditation, 1985-1986 (Box 32:, Folder 1088)
    - Anniversary celebration: 40th, 1988 (Box 32:, Folder 1089)
    - Budget/funding, 1983-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 1090-1091)
    - Faculty meeting minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 32:, Folder 1092)
    - Fee proposal for Fall, 1985 (Box 32:, Folder 1093)
    - General, 1984-1989 (Box 32:, Folder 1094-1098)
    - New England, University of, 1987-1988 (Box 32:, Folder 1099)
    - Northern New England Phase-Out Program meeting, 1986 April 25 (Box 32:, Folder 1100)
    - Northern New England Program, 1984-1986 (Box 32:, Folder 1101-1102)
    - Renovations, 1985 (Box 32:, Folder 1103)
- Series XII: Centers, undated, 1982-1990
  - Academic Programs, Center for
    - Academic Coordinator for Athletes, 1983-1986 (Box 33:, Folder 1104-1106)
    - Analysis of student progression, The Applicant, 1985 May (Box 33:, Folder 1107)
    - Budgets, 1983-1986 (Box 33:, Folder 1108-1109)
    - CONNPEP: CT Precollegiate Enrichment Program, 1984-1986 (Box 33:, Folder 1110-1111)
    - Evaluation assessment, 1987-1988 (Box 33:, Folder 1112)
    - Evaluation report, 1987 (Box 33:, Folder 1113)
    - General, 1984-1989 (Box 33:, Folder 1114-1123)
    - Grants, 1986-1987 (Box 33:, Folder 1124)
    - Management Plan: report, 1985 (Box 33:, Folder 1125)
    - Minority Retention, Center for, 1987-1988 (Box 33:, Folder 1126)
    - Minority Student, Committee for the Evaluation of, 1983 (Box 33:, Folder 1127)
    - Mission statement, undated (Box 33:, Folder 1128)
    - Peer review, 1986-1987 (Box 33:, Folder 1129)
    - Personnel, 1983-1984 (Box 33:, Folder 1130-1131)
    - Program Director, Academic Planning for Student Athletes, 1986 (Box 33:, Folder 1132)
    - Purpose statements, 1985 (Box 33:, Folder 1133)
    - Retreat, 1985 December (Box 33:, Folder 1134)
    - SAEP-CAP transition, 1986 (Box 33:, Folder 1135)
    - Summer Program, 1987 (Box 33:, Folder 1136)
    - Upward Bound, 1986-1990 (Box 33:, Folder 1137)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1982-1988 (Box 33:, Folder 1138-1139)
  - Application of High Technology, Center for, 1982-1983 (Box 33:, Folder 1140-1141)
  - Biotechnology Center, 1986-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1142-1144)
  - Black Studies, Center for, 1985-1987 (Box 34:, Folder 1145-1147)
  - Computer Center
    - Advisory Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 34:, Folder 1148)
    - Computer Committee, 1988 (Box 34:, Folder 1149)
    - Disaster Recovery Planning for Computer Systems, 1988-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1150)
    - IBM Grant Program, 1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1151)
    - Long-Range Computer Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1152-1153)
    - Telecommunications, 1986-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1154-1157)
  - Computer Applications and Research Center, 1983-1985 (Box 34:, Folder 1158-1159)
  - Connecticut Small Business Development Center, 1984-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1160-1166)
  - Educational Innovation, Center for, 1983-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1167-1171)
  - Environmental Health, Center for, 1986-1989 (Box 34:, Folder 1172-1173)
  - Faculty/Staff Development, Center for, 1986-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1174-1175)
  - Instructional Media and Technology, Center for, 1983-1989 (Box 35:, Folder 1176-1186)
  - Insurance Education and Research, Center for, 1984-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1187-1189)
  - International Community Health Studies, Center for, 1985 (Box 35:, Folder 1190)
  - Judaic Studies and Contemporary Jewish Life, Center for, 1984 (Box 35:, Folder 1191)
  - Labor Education, Center for, 1984-1985 (Box 35:, Folder 1192-1193)
  - Latin-American Studies, Center for, 1983-1988 (Box 35:, Folder 1194-1198)
  - Middle East Studies, Center for, 1984, 1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1199-1200)
  - Oral History, Center for, 1983-1984 (Box 35:, Folder 1201)
  - Study of Child Welfare, Center for, 1985 (Box 35:, Folder 1202)
  - Wildlife Diseases, Northeastern Research Center for, 1984-1985 (Box 35:, Folder 1203-1208)
  - Women's Center, 1983-1989 (Box 35:, Folder 1209-1213)
  - World Education Center, I.N. Thut, 1985-1987 (Box 35:, Folder 1214-1216)
- Series XIII: Institutes, 1960-1989
  - African-American Studies, 1987-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1217)
  - Cellular Biology, 1960-1985 (Box 36:, Folder 1218)
  - Environmental Health, 1984-1985 (Box 36:, Folder 1219)
  - Environmental Research, 1987-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1220-1221)
  - Marine Sciences, 1983-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1222-1230)
  - Material Science, 1983-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1231-1240)
  - Public Service, 1985-1986 (Box 36:, Folder 1241-1242)
  - Public and Urban Affairs, 1983-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1243)
  - Social Inquiry, 1983-1989 (Box 36:, Folder 1244-1254)
  - Stratford, 1988 (Box 36:, Folder 1255)
  - Technology, 1983-1984 (Box 36:, Folder 1256)
  - Transportation, 1981-1988 (Box 36:, Folder 1257-1258)
  - Waste Management, 1982-1984 (Box 36:, Folder 1259)
  - Water Resources, 1982-1988 (Box 36:, Folder 1260-1263)
- Series XIV: Library, 1970-1989
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 37:, Folder 1264)
  - Budget/funding, 1985-1988 (Box 37:, Folder 1265)
  - Dodd Papers, 1985-1987 (Box 37:, Folder 1266)
  - Fees, 1989 (Box 37:, Folder 1267)
  - GEAC automation project, 1984-1985 (Box 37:, Folder 1268)
  - General, 1983-1989 (Box 37:, Folder 1269-1274)
  - Ginsberg Archives, 1987 (Box 37:, Folder 1275)
  - Historical Manuscripts and Archives Division, 1983 (Box 37:, Folder 1276)
  - Long Range Plan, 1986-1989 (Box 37:, Folder 1277)
  - Security, 1970-1988 (Box 37:, Folder 1278)
- Series XV: Research Foundation, undated, 1983-1989
  - Connecticut Technology Park: proposal, 1985-1987 (Box 38:, Folder 1279-1281)
  - CoreTech, 1987 (Box 38:, Folder 1282)
  - Corporate/faculty contacts, 1983 (Box 38:, Folder 1283)
  - Director, 1988-1989 (Box 38:, Folder 1284)
  - Eq/matches credit line, 1988 (Box 38:, Folder 1285)
  - General, 1983-1988 (Box 39:, Folder 1286-1291)
  - General, 1988-1989 (Box 40:, Folder 1292)
  - Governor's Technology Advisory Board, 1986-1988 (Box 40:, Folder 1293)
  - Howard Hughes Medical Institute Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 40:, Folder 1294)
  - Master of Public Affairs, 1986 (Box 40:, Folder 1295)
  - Patent and Policy Procedures, 1986 (Box 40:, Folder 1296)
  - Research Advisory Council, 1983-1989 (Box 40:, Folder 1297-1298)
  - R&D Corporation, 1986 (Box 40:, Folder 1299)
  - R&D Expenditures, 1988 (Box 40:, Folder 1300)
  - Technology Transfer Office, 1987-1989 (Box 40:, Folder 1301)
  - University Industry Relations, 1986 (Box 40:, Folder 1302)
  - UTC Agreement, undated (Box 40:, Folder 1303)
- Series XVI: Committees, undated, 1974-1987
  - Academic Advisory Committee, undated (Box 41:, Folder 1304)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Feasibility of Requiring all Undergrads a Level of Competency in the Use of Computers, 1984-1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1305)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for the Study of General Education Requirements for Undergraduates, 1984-1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1306)
  - Admissions Committee, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1307)
  - Animal Care Committee, 1983-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1308)
  - Athletic Advisory Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1309)
  - Building Names Committee, 1987 (Box 41:, Folder 1310)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1983 (Box 41:, Folder 1311)
  - Communications Study Group, 1982 (Box 41:, Folder 1312)
  - Community Relations Committee, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 1313)
  - Computer Proficiency, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1314)
  - ConnTech Advisory Committee, 1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1315-1317)
  - Council of Assistant Deans for Resident Instruction, 1983-1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1318)
  - Energy Committee Advisory Board, 1983 (Box 41:, Folder 1319)
  - Evaluation of the General Education Curriculum Ad Hoc Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 41:, Folder 1320)
  - Exhibits Committee, 1981 (Box 41:, Folder 1321)
  - Faculty/Staff Development Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1322)
  - Fulbright Scholarship Committee, 1980-1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1323)
  - Gerontology, All-University Advisory Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1324)
  - Graduate School and Research Foundation Steering Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1325)
  - Greater University, Committee for a, 1982 (Box 41:, Folder 1326)
  - Honorary Degree Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1327-1328)
  - Information Management Systems Committee, 1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1329)
  - International Education, Advisory Committee on, 1982-1983 (Box 41:, Folder 1330)
  - International Studies, Study of Burke Report on, 1986-1987 (Box 41:, Folder 1331)
  - Master of Public Affairs Advisory Committee, 1977-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1332)
  - Math Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 41:, Folder 1333)
  - MBA Relocation Committee, 1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1334)
  - Minority Affairs Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1335)
  - Molecular and Applied Genetics, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1336)
  - Permanent Oversight Committee on Student Evaluation and Faculty Teaching, 1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1337)
  - President's Advisory Committee on Human Relations, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1338)
  - Radiation Safety Advisory Committee, 1987 (Box 41:, Folder 1339)
  - Sponsored Research and Training, 1983 (Box 41:, Folder 1340)
  - Staff Development, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1341)
  - Telecommunications Committee, 1985 (Box 41:, Folder 1342)
  - Transportation Institute Advisory Committee, 1974-1981 (Box 41:, Folder 1343)
  - Trustee-Administration-Faculty-Student Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1344)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum, 1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1345)
  - University Medal Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 41:, Folder 1346)
  - University Relations Council, 1983-1984 (Box 41:, Folder 1347)
  - Violence Against Women, President's Advisory Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 41:, Folder 1348)
- Series XVII: Long Range Planning Reports, 1983
  - Agriculture and Natural Resources (#10), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1349-1351)
  - Allied Health Professions (#11), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1352)
  - Business Administration (#12), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1353-1354)
  - Centers and Institutes (#25), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1355-1359)
  - Education (#13), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1360-1362)
  - Engineering (#14), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1363-1364)
  - Family Studies (#15), 1983 (Box 42:, Folder 1365)
  - Family Studies (#15), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1366)
  - Fine Arts (#16), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1367)
  - Law (#17), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1368)
  - Liberal Arts and Sciences (#18), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1369-1371)
  - Liberal Arts and Sciences (#19), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1372-1375)
  - Library (#24), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1376)
  - Nursing (#20), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1377)
  - Opportunities for the '80s (#26), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1378-1380)
  - Pharmacy (#21), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1381)
  - Regional Campuses (#23), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1382-1383)
  - Social Work (#22), 1983 (Box 43:, Folder 1384)
- Series XVIII: Department of Higher Education, 1979-1989
  - Architecture, School of, 1984 (Box 44:, Folder 1385)
  - Assessment Activities at Universities and Colleges, 1988 (Box 44:, Folder 1386)
  - Biotechnology application, 1988 (Box 44:, Folder 1387)
  - Budget option for 1988, 1986-1987 (Box 44:, Folder 1388)
  - Budget priorities from 1991, 1986-1989 (Box 44:, Folder 1389)
  - Centers for Excellence, 1986-1989 (Box 44:, Folder 1390-1394)
  - CONNCAP proposals, 1986 (Box 44:, Folder 1395)
  - CT State University, 1979-1985 (Box 44:, Folder 1396)
  - Cost equity funding, 1987 (Box 44:, Folder 1397)
  - Distinguished Teacher Program, 1985 (Box 44:, Folder 1398)
  - Ed.D. Study, 1984-1985 (Box 44:, Folder 1399)
  - Endowed Chairs, 1986-1987 (Box 44:, Folder 1400)
  - Fairfield County higher education needs, 1988 (Box 44:, Folder 1401)
  - Formula Budgeting, 1984-1987 (Box 44:, Folder 1402-1404)
  - Find for Excellence, 1984-1986 (Box 44:, Folder 1405-1407)
  - General, 1984-1989 (Box 45:, Folder 1408-1416)
  - Governor's Technology Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 45:, Folder 1417)
  - HEIS Advisory Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 45:, Folder 1418)
  - High Technology Equipment and Doctoral Fellowships, proposal for, 1986-1988 (Box 45:, Folder 1419)
  - High Technology Project, 1983-1988 (Box 45:, Folder 1420-1422)
  - Higher Education Information Systems Advisory Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 45:, Folder 1423)
  - Institutional Assessment Committee, 1987-1989 (Box 45:, Folder 1424)
  - International Exchange Program, 1986 (Box 45:, Folder 1425)
  - Library Services Formula, 1987 (Box 45:, Folder 1426)
  - Licensure and Accreditation, Special Advisory Committee on, 1985-1988 (Box 45:, Folder 1427-1431)
  - Minority Student Access and Retention Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 46:, Folder 1432)
  - Mission, Role and Scope Guidelines Ad Hoc Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 46:, Folder 1433-1440)
  - Mission statements, 1986 (Box 46:, Folder 1441)
  - Mission statement: revised, 1986 September 5 (Box 46:, Folder 1442)